<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Work on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Work on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Bot Classifier (Edgio)</title>
      <link>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/bot_classifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/bot_classifier/</guid>
      <description>Bot Classifier I created and automated a Bot-or-Not Classification Model for Edgio, allowing customers to defend against more sophisticated bots based on a configurable threshold. For our client Shoe Carnival, our ML-powered bot solution blocked 8M malicious requests in one month and reduced security exploit mitigation time by 85%. See details on the bot solution here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Body Validation (Edgio)</title>
      <link>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/api_security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/api_security/</guid>
      <description>Secured customer APIs by implementing configurable JSON Schema Validation + Rules. Above is a view of the frontend deployed for the solution, along with the page for rule violations. See details on the deployed solution here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien Invasion</title>
      <link>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/sidescroller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/sidescroller/</guid>
      <description>Sidescroller Written in C++ using the Qt Creator and an Event-Driven Programming Scheme. This Project was completed in collaboration with Darren Atallah, Weiyu Huang, and Peter Liu. Among other things, I was responsible for handling user input, player abilities, and optimizing program efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect4 AI</title>
      <link>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/connect4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vrobbins.github.io/projects/connect4/</guid>
      <description>Connect-4 with AI and Graphical User Interface This is a Connect-4 AI written in Java and implementing a Minimax Algorithm with Alpha-Beta Pruning. With difficulty = 4 and under 100,000 distinct games, this AI beats a random AI 99.983% of the time and loses 0.013% of the time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
